{
    "id": "5057c8d28a864c248e1fc9af0baf1661",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They printed these books. These books ………………….. by them.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
            "answers": [
                "are printed",
                "have been printed",
                "were printed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c5d3bf6b2ead44ff936ec28b08eaadd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Clean the room. Let the room …………………….",
            "description": "Passive forms of imperatives are made with be + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "cleaned",
                "be cleaned",
                "is cleaned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8dc9dc1b77547bbac7c8bd96cf501af"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher reprimanded the boy. The boy …………………….. by the teacher.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
            "answers": [
                "reprimanded",
                "was reprimanded",
                "has reprimanded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0eaca98dd2924509aab614d45dc15c05"
        },
        {
            "question": "They will announce the results in the afternoon. Results ……………………….. in the afternoon.",
            "description": "In the simple future, the passive form is made by putting will + be before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "will announced",
                "are announced",
                "will be announced"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2d449434766f4371ae5f2a106afcbf4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody hates him. He …………………….. by everybody.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, we make the passive form with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "hates",
                "is hating",
                "is hated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f273f485e0e1400fba9225b43b647397"
        },
        {
            "question": "The monkey is eating a banana. A banana …………………….. by the monkey.",
            "description": "In the present continuous, we make the passive form by putting is/am/are + being before the past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is eaten",
                "is being eaten",
                "was being eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "013fb2d0d47542f6aad979dfb346cfe6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government will build a bridge. A bridge …………………….. by the government.",
            "description": "In the simple future, the passive form is made by putting will + be before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "will be build",
                "will be built",
                "will be building"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fccc89f4ddf34a38ab37d1be13df5227"
        },
        {
            "question": "She gave me a book. I …………………… a book by her.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
            "answers": [
                "gave",
                "was given",
                "have given"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ce20fb001f04faea75340004305d07c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She cheated him. He ……………………. by her.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
            "answers": [
                "was cheated",
                "has cheated",
                "had cheated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f97133218fe444519aee4c52e1797326"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have sent the parcel. The parcel ………………………….. by me.",
            "description": "In the present perfect tense, the passive form is made by putting has/have + been before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has sent",
                "has been sent",
                "have been sent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b44b94cf336441b8a7c5f8176530f9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has composed a song. A song ………………………. by him.",
            "description": "In the present perfect tense, the passive form is made by putting has/have + been before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is composed",
                "has been composed",
                "is being composed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b92027c8f25040e08b6e71d0ede69304"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked him to get out. He ………………………. by the teacher to get out.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
            "answers": [
                "was asked",
                "has asked",
                "has been asked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21a94e6905614dcb8782dd70ab7f10a0"
        }
    ]
}